Guide to the Roger Sherman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- BUSINESS PAPERS, 1842-1907; Series II; 7.75' (20 boxes)
  - Chronological
    - 1894 April-1895 October (Box 41, Folder 321-333)
    - 1895 November-1896 June (Box 42, Folder 334-342)
    - 1896 July-1897 February 8 (Box 43, Folder 343-351)
    - 1897 February 9-Sep, undated (Box 44, Folder 352-356)
  - Account Books
    - Journal, 1872-1873 (Box 45, Folder 357)
    - Journal B, 1874 (Box 45, Folder 358)
    - Journal C, 1875-1876 (Box 45, Folder 359)
    - Journal D, 1876-1877 (Box 45, Folder 360)
    - Journal E, 1878-1879 (Box 45, Folder 361)
    - Journal G, 1884-1897 (Box 46, Folder 362)
    - Ledger D, 1881-1897 (Box 46, Folder 363)
    - Trial balances, 1884-1899 (Box 46, Folder 364)
    - Minor and Sherman—journal, 1883-1907 (Box 46, Folder 365)
    - Minor and Sherman—ledger, 1883-1907 (Box 47, Folder 366)
    - Sherman and Beebe—ledger, 1885-1895 (Box 47, Folder 367)
    - Funk Farm Oil Co.—journal, 1889-1895 (Box 47, Folder 368)
    - Funk Farm Oil Co.—ledger, 1889-1895 (Box 47, Folder 369)
    - Roger Sherman—journal, 1893-1897 (Box 48, Folder 370)
    - Roger Sherman—ledger, 1893-1898 (Box 48, Folder 371)
    - Unidentified, 1872, 1878-1897 (Box 48, Folder 372)
  - Other books
    - Docket book, 1871-1873, 1872-1883 (Box 49, Folder 373-374)
    - Justice docket; claim register, 1872-1873 (Box 50, Folder 375)
    - Execution docket, 1873-1880 (Box 50, Folder 376)
    - Claim docket, 1876-1890 (Box 50, Folder 377)
    - Register—releases for rights of way and liens, 1877 (Box 50, Folder 378)
    - Exchange Bank of Titusville—dividend payment record, 1877-1888 (Box 50, Folder 379)
    - Index to office papers, 1886, undated (Box 51, Folder 380)
    - Trial lists, 1888, undated (Box 51, Folder 381)
    - Orion Oil Co.—minute book, 1890 (Box 51, Folder 382)
- PERSONAL AND FAMILY PAPERS, 1770-1935; Series III; 6.25' (15 boxes)
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by the names of individual family members.
  - Conkling Family, 1828-1884 (Box 52, Folder 384-387)
  - Phillips, Thomas W., 1920-1935 (Box 52, Folder 388-389)
  - Seymour, C. B.
    - Correspondence, 1875-1907 (Box 52, Folder 390)
    - re: Helen Barker, 1869 (Box 52, Folder 391-392)
    - Souvenir booklets from the World's Columbian Exposition, 1893 (Box 52, Folder 393)
    - Souvenir booklets from the World's Columbian Exposition, 1893 (Box 53, Folder 394-395)
  - Sherman, Alma Seymour
    - Correspondence, 1865-1922, undated (Box 53, Folder 396-399)
    - Children's Aid Society of Crawford County, 1898-1906 (Box 53, Folder 400)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1909, 1921-1922 (Box 53, Folder 401-403)
    - Financial papers, 1897-1916 (Box 53, Folder 404)
    - Financial papers, 1897-1915 (Box 54, Folder 405-416)
    - Main Street Shakepearean Club, 1883-1888 (Box 54, Folder 417)
    - Speeches, 1896,1899,1909 (Box 55, Folder 418)
    - Titusville Relief Auxillary, 1892-1894 (Box 55, Folder 419-420)
    - Titusville Women's Club, 1904-1906 (Box 55, Folder 421)
    - Travelers' Club, 1886-1895 (Box 55, Folder 422)
    - Women's Aid Society of the Presbyterian Church, 1894-1896 (Box 55, Folder 423)
    - XL CLub, 1890-1891 (Box 55, Folder 424)
  - Sherman, Isaac
    - Correspondence, 1828-1841 (Box 55, Folder 425)
    - Correspondence, 1842-1862 (Box 56, Folder 426)
    - Financial and legal papers, 1820-1842 (Box 56, Folder 427-428)
  - Sherman, Nancy C. (Owens), 1807-1858 (Box 56, Folder 430-433)
  - Sherman, Phoebe, undated (Box 56, Folder 434)
  - Sherman, Roger
    - Account books, 1880-1881 (Box 56, Folder 435-436)
    - Account books, 1894-1896 (Box 57, Folder 437-438)
    - American Citizen, 1885-1889, undated (Box 57, Folder 439)
    - Bank book, 1893-1896 (Box 57, Folder 440)
    - Correspondence, personal, 1856-1887 (Box 57, Folder 441-452)
    - Correspondence, personal, 1888-1897, undated (Box 58, Folder 453-462)
    - Diaries, 1887-1896 (Box 58, Folder 463)
    - Library, 1892-1894 (Box 58, Folder 464)
    - Library, 1871-1894 (Box 59, Folder 465-468)
    - Library, 1880-1883 (Box 60, Folder 469-471)
    - Library, 1896-1897 (Box 61, Folder 472-474)
    - Main Street Shakespearean Club, 1881-1884 (Box 61, Folder 475-478)
    - Main Street Shakespearean Club, 1883-1884 (Box 62, Folder 479)
    - Memorials, undated (Box 62, Folder 480)
    - Miscellaneous personal papers, undated (Box 62, Folder 481-482)
    - Photographs, 1892, undated (Box 62, Folder 483-485)
    - Reminiscences, undated (Box 62, Folder 486)
    - Scholastic expenses, 1896-1897 (Box 63, Folder 487)
    - Sons of the American Revolution, 1892-1897 (Box 63, Folder 488)
    - Titusville Centennial, 1889 (Box 63, Folder 489)
    - Titusville Library Association, 1897 (Box 63, Folder 490)
    - Titusville Relief Association, undated (Box 63, Folder 491)
    - Writings, 1887-1896, undated (Box 63, Folder 492-493)
  - Sherman, Roger Seymour
    - Account book, 1912-1917 (Box 63, Folder 494)
    - Correspondence, 1898-1908, undated (Box 63, Folder 495)
    - Legal notebooks, undated (Box 63, Folder 496-497)
    - Legal notebooks, undated (Box 64, Folder 498-507)
    - Legal notebooks, undated (Box 65, Folder 508-511)
    - School notebook, 1898-1899 (Box 65, Folder 512)
    - Sons of the American Revolution, 1896 (Box 65, Folder 513)
    - Titusville school notebook, undated (Box 65, Folder 514)
  - Family, miscellaneous, 1852-1861, undated (Box 65, Folder 515)
  - Unidentified manuscript, undated (Box 66, Folder 516-524)
  - Printed material, miscellaneous, 1770-1916, undated (Box 66, Folder 525-531)
- SCRAPBOOKS, 1870-1897; Series IV; 5.0' (12 boxes)
  This series contains material arranged in two sections: Volumes and Miscellanea. Volumes contains twenty-three numbered and individually indexed items. They are arranged in numerical order. Miscellanea contains two boxes of memorabilia arranged in chronological order.
  - Volumes
    - 1-3, 1870-1879 (Box 67, Folder 532-534)
    - 4-6, 1879-1889 (Box 68, Folder 535-537)
    - 7-9, 1880-1895 (Box 69, Folder 538-540)
    - 10-11, 1878-1897 (Box 70, Folder 541-542)
    - 12-13, 1888-1895 (Box 71, Folder 543-544)
    - 14-15, 1880-1895 (Box 72, Folder 545-546)
    - 16-17, 1866-1896 (Box 73, Folder 547-548)
    - 18-19, 1865-1895 (Box 74, Folder 549-550)
    - 20-21, 1886-1897 (Box 75, Folder 551-552)
    - 22-23, 1894, 1896-1897 (Box 76, Folder 553-554)
  - Miscellanea
    - Invitations, calling cards, etc., 1880s (Box 77, Folder 555)
    - Invitations, calling cards, etc., 1890s (Box 78, Folder 556)
- OVERSIZE
  - Business Papers
    - Chronological, 1854-1877 (Box 79)
    - Chronological, 1878-1897, undated (Box 79)
    - Other books (Box 79)
  - Personal and Family Papers
    - Conkling family (Box 79)
    - Sherman, Alma Janet (Box 79)
    - Sherman, Alma Seymour (Box 79)
    - Sherman, Roger (Box 79)